

MOHIT GUPTA

Frontend Developer

G-1, 55/A, Sai Enclave, Mohan Garden, Uttam Nagar, N.D.-110059

9625118538

⊠ guptamohit2206@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 22/06/1994, New Delhi Nationality Indian

Skills

HTML5, CSS, JS, jQuery,
Bootstrap, WordPress,
Google Page Speed,
Outlook mailer & HTML
Mailer, Scss-sass,
Tailwind, React JS,
Adobe Photoshop & XD
PSD to Wordpress,
PSD to Html,
Time management
Deadline-driven
Effective communicator
Team player

Energetic and inventive

Profile

Energetic Web Designer with 3 years experience creating and maintaining functional, attractive, and responsive websites for companies. Clear understanding of modern technologies and best design practices. Experienced with WordPress and Bootstrap. Experienced Frontend Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry..

Employment History

Frontend Developer, Touchstone Infotech, Delhi

March 2019 — August 2020

Touchstone Infotech is Web Design & Development Service and Digital Marketing Agency company. As the Frontend Developer, my core activities included:

- Creating homepage assets for both desktop & mobile experiences
- Designing images, icons, and banners & Content arrange.
- Presenting concepts and ideas consistent with company branding guidelines to the creative team.

Frontend Developer, Brand Provoke, Noida

August 2020 — Present

As a strategic brand consultancy and branding agency. As the Frontend Developer, my core activities included:

- Designing, building, and maintaining marketing email creative using data-driven responsive sites.
- Providing expertise on industry standards, best practices, and proper coding techniques to achieve correct rendering in all email environments.
- Performing quality assurance and troubleshooting code rendering across multiple desktop and mobile devices.
- Creating landing pages using WordPress CMS and HTML.

Education

10th, CBSE, Delhi

2010-2012

12th, CBSE, Arts, Delhi

2014

BCA 3rd year, IGNOU, Delhi

2022

· Software Engineering.

Courses

Smart Professional E-commerce, Aptech Computer Education

August 2018

Website Work

Sites Web Links

Backlinks https://www.backlink-market.com/

Thehappyhogar https://thehappyhogar.com/
First-advertising https://first-advertising.com/

Planova https://planova.com/

GRSL India https://www.grslindia.com/
Homespital https://homespital.org.in/
Talentzone talentzoneacademy.com/
Hotcerts https://hotcerts.com/affiliates

Amd40 https://amd40.com/

Acuity Risk Conslt. https://acuity-test-app.vercel.app/dashboard

Garitransfer https://garitransfer.com/private-tours

Declaration

I here by declare that all information given above is correct according to the best of my knowledge and belief.

DATE:- _/_/2022 (Mohit)